https://www.sitcomsonline.com/policy.html

Privacy Statement for
Sitcoms Online
Sitcoms Online
has created this privacy
statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy.
The following discloses the information gathering and
dissemination practices for this Web site:
Sitcoms Online
We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our web site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit networkadvertising.org .
We're affiliates of Google AdSense, Amazon.com and VigLink.
We show non-personalized ads for visitors from EU countries.
Information Automatically Logged
We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer our Web site.
Cookies
Our Site uses cookies to save your password so you don't have to re-enter it each time you visit our site.
Advertisers
We use an outside ad company to display ads on our site. These ads may contain cookies.
While we use cookies in other parts of our Web site, cookies received with banner ads are
collected by our ad company, and we do not have access to this information.
Personal Information
This Web site does not request any personal information or collect any information that personally
identifies you or allows you to be personally contacted.
Since we do not collect any personal information on this Web site, we do not share any personal
information with any third parties nor do we use any personal information for any purposes.
External Links
This site contains links to other sites.
Sitcoms Online
is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites.
Public Forums
This site makes chat rooms, forums, message boards, and/or news groups available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information.
Security
This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control.
Children's Guidelines
We care about children and understand that they have
special privacy needs.
Therefore, we have adopted the following
privacy policy regarding children:
We will NOT collect, use, or distribute to third parties
personally identifiable information without prior verifiable parental
consent.
We will NOT give the child access to unmonitored chat
rooms, message boards, email accounts, or other services that would
give the child the ability to publicly post or otherwise distribute
personally identifiable information without prior verifiable parental
consent
When verifiable parental consent is not obtained, we
will only use the online contact information (such as email) to:
Respond directly to the child's request on a one-time
basis and not use that information to re-contact the
child for other purposes.
Request the name or online contact information of a
parent for the purpose of obtaining verifiable parental
consent or providing parental notification.
Respond more than once directly to a specific request
from a child (such as in the case where a child requests
a newsletter subscription) and not used to re-contact the
child for other purposes.
We will use our best efforts
to provide parental notification, which will include the
nature and intended use as well as an opportunity for the
parent to prevent the use of the information and
participation in the activity.
We will NOT entice the child to divulge more information than
is needed to participate in any activity, game, or service.
We will provide the parent a description of the specific
types of a personally identifiable information collected from
their child upon request.
We will allow the parent to refuse
further use or future online collection of personally
identifiable information and provide a way for a parent to
obtain any personally identifiable information collected from
their child.
We will provide notice to children in age appropriate
terms of what personally identifiable information is to be
collected.
We will NOT provide any links to Web sites that are
unsuitable for children.
We will encourage children to get their parent's
permission before sharing personal information online.
Contacting the Web Site
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact:
